module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'What was the original name of Whole Foods?', 
    a: 'Organic Grocers',
    b: 'SaferWay',
    c: 'Mackey\'s Market',
    d: 'Trader Ho\'s',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'During WWII, who created an experimental weapon that consisted of attaching bombs to Mexican free-tail bats?', 
    a: 'a dentist',
    b: 'a biochemist',
    c: 'a lawyer',
    d: 'Troy',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the term for where bats sleeps?', 
    a: 'a den',
    b: 'a roost',
    c: 'a lil bat bed',
    d: 'a fold',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What was the original capital of the Republic of Texas?', 
    a: 'Houston',
    b: 'San Antonio',
    c: 'Always been Austin',
    d: 'Lubbock',
    answer: 'a'
  },
    {
    question: 'In 1842, who ordered troops to steal the national archives from Austin, and bring them to Houston to effectively make it the capital (only to be stopped by a posse from Austin)', 
    a: 'Mirabeau B. Lamar',
    b: 'Rafael Vásquez',
    c: 'Sam Houston',
    d: 'David Bowie',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the record high temperature recorded in Austin?', 
    a: '110',
    b: '112',
    c: '120',
    d: '212',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Under the Köppen climate classification, Austin\'s climate is a...', 
    a: 'hot desert climate',
    b: 'mild semi-arid climate',
    c: 'humid subtropical climate',
    d: 'subtropical highland climate',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'On Feb 4, 2011, how many inches of snow did Austin receive that caused over 300 car accidents?', 
    a: '0.9 inches',
    b: '2.4 inches',
    c: '5.1 inches',
    d: '7.3 inches',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'In 2016, the American Community Survey estimated what percentage of Austin commuters use public transit?', 
    a: '3.6%',
    b: '5.1%',
    c: '7.8%',
    d: '10.1%',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'When the first SXSW was held in 1987, how many attendees came?', 
    a: '100',
    b: '350',
    c: '700',
    d: '1500',
    answer: 'c'
  },
];